bighip.com 2012-06-14

# BigHip: Privacy Policy

| 

Privacy Policy

Big Hip is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers. 

The purpose of this Big Hip privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to BigHip.com, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. 

The following divulges our tactic in capturing information and usage practices for Big Hip. Big Hip offers several opportunities for visitors to join for promotional and informational mailings or to receive assistance in evaluating our email solutions and services. We use this contact information to send information about our company and its products and services. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time and it takes less than 72 hours for your email to be removed. 

Unsolicited commercial e-mail is forbidden by Big Hip, Inc. 

Capturing Information

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We also track browser types to help us understand our visitors' needs related to our web site design. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. All captured information helps us determine your needs related to our solutions. We also use this information to send updates about our company, our products or services. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; below every email is the choice to opt-out. In less than 72 hours your email is removed from our database. 

IP Addresses

IP addresses are tracked to help monitor user sessions. We use this information to see how user interactivity is being conducted to better service our customers. The personal information of specific users remains anonymous and is not linked to the IP address. 

Cookies

Client-side cookies are used to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website. Client-side cookies are also used to track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs or to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. All set cookies are temporary; once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site; however, the user may be limited to the access of some areas within our website. 

Sharing & Usage

Big Hip is the sole owner of the information collected and we do not sell, share, or rent this information to others without your advanced permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you e-mails based on your request for information. 

Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Big Hip takes care to reinforce the importance of our web site visitors' security and privacy among our employees. We are constantly re-evaluating and deploying new technologies to enhance our security. 

Choice / Opt-out

Big Hip provides users the opportunity to opt-in and opt-out of receiving communications from us. This is made available during sign-up for our e-mail lists and in all e-mail messages delivered from our company, or you can email us at support@bighip.com. Once a user opts-out, the user will no longer receive future communications. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may unsubscribe at any time either by clicking on the unsubscribe link, available in all our mailings, or by sending an email to unsubsribe@bighip.com. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our clients can make an nformed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

|
